strife.com 2014-02-22

# Strife - Home - Privacypolicy

## Privacy Policy

S2 Games, LLC., heretofore "S2 Games," provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our privacy policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT IS NOTICE OF: 

• What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website 

• The organization collecting the information 

• How the information is used 

• With whom the information may be shared 

• What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 

• The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under S2 Games' control 

• How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact S2 Games by EMAIL at privacy@s2games.com. 

Strife (hereinafter "Strife") is composed of the software program, and any files that are delivered to you by S2 Games, LLC (herein referred to as S2 or S2 Games), via on-line transmission or otherwise, to "patch," update, or otherwise modify the software program, as well as any printed materials and any on-line or electronic documentation (the "Manual"), and any and all copies and derivative works of such software program and Manual (collectively, the "Game") and is the copyrighted work of S2 Games, LLC and its subsidiaries, affiliates or its licensors. The website, http://www.strife.com, all related sites, online play environments, including but not limited to S2 servers, and related activities in and of S2 Games, are the sole and exclusive property of S2 Games, LLC. Your use of S2 games and services is subject at all times to these Terms of Service (TOS), or Privacy Policy (PP) and/or our Beta Policy (BP) which are incorporated herein by reference. The Game is distributed solely for use by authorized end users according to the provisions of this TOS. Any use, reproduction, modification or distribution of the Game not expressly authorized by the terms of the TOS, or without the prior written consent of S2, is expressly prohibited. If you have questions about the Terms of Service, please contact us by sending an email to TOS@s2games.com 

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE.

S2 Games is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. S2 Games collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

COOKIES.

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to participate in any of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

LOG FILES.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

SHARING.

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

LINKS.

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that S2 GAMES is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

NEWSLETTER.

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

SURVEYS AND CONTENTS.

From time to time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

TELL-A-FRIEND.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. S2 GAMES will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. S2 GAMES stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact S2 GAMES at remove@s2games.com to request the removal of this information from their database. 

CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support. 

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
